Guide to the University Historical Material records, 1821-2012 RG0031
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Images and visual works, 1859-1990; RG0031 Series 1; 21 Linear feet (Box 1, Box 2, Box 3, Box 4, Box 5, Box 22, Box 23, Box 24, Box 34, Flat box 37, Box 42, Box 86, Box 95, Box 205, Box 206, Box 265, Box 267, Box 268, Box 269, Box 270, Box 271, Box 87, Flat box 89, Flat box 90, Box 91, Box 92, Box
  - NEGATIVES, Box 229: See note for contents, RG0031 Series 1 (Box 229)
    74: Students standing outside Student Union building, c.1960 75: Biochemistry Lab. and students viewing gastro-intesinal system 76: Men's Dorm, two men in room 77: Counseling Center and Students at center 79: Language Lab 80: Women's Dorm, two girls in room 81: Athletics: Women's Sports Collage, c.1950 82: Athletics: Men's sports Collage 83: Camp Hill House, Meridian Hill hospital - Picture, c1862 84: Soliders standing in front of tents, original Columbian College building in background 85: Columbian Law building just before being torn down, 1898 86: George Whitefield Samson, D.D. 87: S.W. Corner 21st & G Sts., N.W., c.1912 88: 15th Street, NW looking north from Penn. Ave., old Columbian University building on right, 1906 89: Woodhull House 90: Porter House 91: Engraving of Spencer Houghton Cone 92: Van Ness Mansion 93: Pres. William Miller Collier 94: Camp of New York 7th Regiment: 2: 95: Medical School Building, H Street between 13th and 14th built by W.W. Corcoran - drawing, c.1870 96: William Staughton 97: Eye St. buildings, c.1910 98: Art Department; Student Painting 99: Foggy Bottom, NW corner of 25th and E Streets, Jan 1913 100: 1925 F Street, N.W., 1912 101: Proposed new law building, c.1945 102: ROTC (?) 103: University Yard, Lisner Hall, c.1950 104: Collage of Monuments around Washington D.C. 105: William Staughton 106: Charles H. Stockton 107: Women's Dorm, two women in room 108: Prof. Frank Weida 109: Lisner Auditorium stage, viewed from a sound proof booth 110: Faculty and Senior Law Class of National University, 1909-10: 5: 111: Unidentified Building 112: Lisner Hall, c.1945 113: Garden behind Lisner Auditorium 114: Students enjoying lunch in Student Union 115: Students around Hall of Government (?) 116: Two people dancing 117: 2 students in lab 118: Presidents of G.W.: 18: 119: Washington conference on theoretical physics, 4th, Mar. 17-19, 1938, 1938 120: Washington conference on theoretical physics, 10th, 1947 121: Washington conference on theoretical physics, 10th, Nov. 13-15, 1947, 1947 122: Washington conference on theoretical physics, 9th, Oct.31-Nov.2, 1946, 1946 123: Washington conference on theoretical physics, 6th, Mar.21-23, 1940, 1940 124: Washington conference on theoretical physics, 5th, Jan.26-28, 1938, 1939 125: Washington conference on theoretical physics, 4th,, 1938 126: Washington conference on theoretical physics, 3rd, Feb.20-25, 1937, 1937 127: Washington conference on theoretical physics, 2nd, Apr.27-29, 1936, 1936 128: Dr. George Gamow receiving certificate of appreciation from Gen. Arnold: 2: 129: Group shot of Law School faculty; Walter S. Cox,William A Maury, John Marshall Harlan, David Josiah Brewer 130: Alex Y.P. Garnett, 1851 131: Harvey Lindsly 132: President Eisenhower receiving honorary degree from Pres. Carroll: 2: 133: Elliot School Faculty (c.1910) and studetns (c.1965): 3: 134: President George W. Sampson 135: J. William Fulbright, LLB 1934, c.1970 136: Judge Joyce Hens Green, LLB 1951, U.S. District Court of DC 137: Dean Joseph Metivier, 1974 138: Lois Schwoerer 139: Dean Walter A. Bloedorn with Pres. Marvin, March 23, 48 140: Helen Newman: 3: 1925 141: Dr. Parks (not John); Med. School 142: Basil Pollit, 1923 143: Telethon at Lisner Auditoium - Andy Williams, Robert Kennedy, Perry Como, Ted Kennedy, Eddie Fisher, 1968 144: Pres. Marvin laying cornerstone for Lisner Auditorium, 1941 145: William Patrick Johnston 146: John P. Adams M.D.: 3: 147: Marcus Cunliffe, 1982 148: Louis Schwoerer 149: Henry Grattan Doyle 150: Adoniram Judson Hutington 151: Elliott School Faculty; Charles Swisher, Arthur Burns, Elmer Kayser, C. Veditz, W. West, Burton Sapin, Hiram Stout, Charles Hill: 8: 152: General Lafayette 153: L. Ron Hubbard, GW chapter American Society of Civil Engineers, 1931 154: L. Ron Hubbard, in group photo - MISSING 5/01, 1931 155: School of Business and Public Management 156: Original Columbian University building 157: Strong Hall 158: Lisner Hall 159: Glee Club 160: Student Union building 161: Picture of unidentified woman 162: 21st and G St., NW, looking east, Woodhull House, Bell Hall, Lisner Hall, Stuart Hall, c.1950 163: Hospital from Washington Circle:: c.1950 164: Two men talking to one another 165: An Officer operating the logistics computer 166: View of Columbian College building and President's House during Civil War, c.1862 167: Law School, "Moot Court" 168: Hatchet- Vol I, No. 2 - cover, 10/12/1904 169: Pres. William Collier 170: Two women and a man 171: Picture of a world map 172: Two men and a woman 173: Man handing another man a plaque 174: Bill Reinhart giving most valuable player award trophy, c.1962 175: Microfiche - Airlie Foundation 176: Preservation techniques being demonstrated: 28: 177: Preservation techniques being demonstrated: 7: 178: MarvinCenter exhibit - pages from 1930 Cherry Tree, 1917, 1931, 1943, 1965 Hatchets: 6: 179: Pres. Marvin speaking at missle site 180: Allegany Project Personnel 181: Allegany Project Missile Launcher Site 182: Allegany Project site, Western Virginia 183: Allegany Project, plane with missiles 184: Allegany Project, missiles on plane wing, 1945 185: Allegany Project, missile components 186: Ben Franklin University, C.P.A Problem class 187: Ben Franklin University, A typical class group 188: Ben Franklin University, Accountancy students at work 189: Ben Franklin University, Basketball team 1927-28 190: Ben Franklin University, Mrs. Thomas Kennedy, President 191: Ben Franklin University- Students studying in library 192: Transportation building, site of BFU 193: Ben Franklin Univ. Building on 16th and L Street, NW, 1976-1977 194: Benjamin Frankiln University in aerial view of Washington 195: John Thomas Kennedy, founder of Ben Franklin Uni. 196: Fred A. L. Schade, Champion Bicyclist from Columbian Call, 1895 197: Sketch of Pres. Lincoln's death chamber 138A: Pres. Truman and wife Bess with two men, c.1946 197A: Lisner auditorium, c.1970 197B: John Quincy Adams 197C: Mt. Vernon College reunion of alumnae, c.1930, c.1930 197D: Thurston Hall (formerly Park Central hotel), c.1965 197E: Aerial view of Foggy Bottom, Nov 1 1976
  - NEGATIVES, Box 230: See note for contents, RG0031 Series 1 (Box SHARED Box 22, Box 230)
    198: Pres. Stephen Joel Trachtenberg 199: Pres. Lloyd Hartman Elliot 200: Pres. Charles Herbert Stockton: 1 201: Pres. William Staughton: 1 202: Pres. Thomas Henry Carroll 203: Joseph Getchell Binney 204: Pres. George Whiterfield Samson 205: Pres. Joel Smith Bacon 206: Pres. William Mather Lewis 207: Pres. Benaiah L. Whitman 208: Pres. William Miller Collier 209: Pres. Stephen Chapin 210: Pres. Oswald Symster Colcough 211: Pres. James Clarke Welling 212: Pres. Samuel Harrison Greene 213: Pres. Cloyd Heck Marvin 214: Pres. Charles Willis Needham,: 215: Pres. Howard L. Hodgkins,: 216: Cheerleaders - overhead view 217: Two women studying in dorm room 218: Construction work on site of Hall of Government 219: Construction work - Lisner Auditorium 220: Ice Skaters from the Women's Athletics Department after precision routine, 1941 221: Student protest, c.1970 222: Classroom scene, c.1965 223: Gathering at the University Quad, c.1930 224: Lynda Baines Johnson and Warrie Lynn Smith arrive for classes outside the School of Government, c.1965 225: Lisner library, Bell and Stuart Halls, c.1940 226: Marvin Center 227: Neophyte Delts pose with chapter founders 228: Eleven new golden keys - women in formal gowns 229: Brothers and Pledges of Pika 230: Graduates, c.1925 231: Offices of student organizations, c.1925 232: Intefraternity Prom, Mar 21,1924 233: Panhellenic Association - Hosford, Jones, Breuniger, Swartwout, Metzerott, Schaaff, Coughlin, Walter,: 1920 234: Philippinesians, c.1940 235: Barry Goldwater chatting with another man, c.1964 236: Phi Sigma Kappa members, c.1965 237: Gamma Chi Chapter, Kappa Kappa Gamma, c.1965 238: Glee Club members, c.1950 239: Jacqueline Kennedy, c.1961 240: School of Government, c.1950 241: Student Unrest, Strike day at Lafyette Park, 1970 242: Sound proof room in Lisner Auditorium Radio Studio, 1944 243: Pres. Trachtenberg talking to children on his way to his first opening convocation:: 1989 244: Ice Skaters from the Women's Athletics Department after precision routine, 1941 245: Banks of the Anacostia River:: 245: Community Service Day, students picking up trash 246: Football game, Tuffy Leemans running past two defenders, 1934 247: Luther Rice silhouette 248: Women's basketball team, 1925, c.1915 249: Man standing in front of the Medical School 250: Pres. Elliot observing an ongoing construction work of Marvin Center, c.1969 251: Student unrest, 1969 252: Students working in a lab. 253: Images from book "Strength to Strength",: 254: Physical education class and classroom lecture 255: Text copy from a year book of faculty members, c.1950 256: Classroom lecture, c.1950 257: Medical students playing cards:: 258: Dr. George Gamow at chalk board, c.1950 259: Cartoon drawings from a year book of campus buildings 260: Text copy from a year book of faculty members, c.1950 261: Margaret Truman and Jane Lingo reading a book, 1946 262: Classroom lecture in Medical School 263: Listing of the Hatchet staff, c.1950 264: Photos of seniors, c.1950 265: Faculty listing 266: Group of students in a classroom 267: Kenneth Winston Starr, 1969 268: Kenneth Winston Starr with a group 269: Women Cheer leaders 270: Laboratory Scene, the School of Medicine 271: Medical School, 1335 H Street, NW (man entering front door), 1964 272: School of Medicine, 1954 273: Hospital on H St., NW - private room, c.1900 274: Operating room of the University Hospital on H Street, c1900 275: Medical School, war time photo 276: Medical students of 1961 entrance ticket 277: Medical School construction site, c.1970 278: Class of 1883, the Medical School 280: Medical School dedication of site for the school and the library, 2/15/71 281: Medical School dedication of site for the school and the library, 2/15/71 282: Ticket of Matriculation, National College of Medicine, 1866-67 283: Practical Anatomy, by W.B.Dorinkard 284: Lecture and Professor's list, The Medical School 285: National Medical College, Lecture on Therapeutics, 1866-67 286: Washington Conf. on Theoretical Physics 3/17/1938, 1938 287: H St. Hospital Bldg, 1902 288: Red Auerbach, basketball team #22, 1940 289: Stockton Hall, c.1955 290: Daniel Inouye, 1952 291: Daniel Inouye, Phi Delta Phi, 1952 292: Daniel Inouye, 1952 293: Basketball team, 1954, 1954 294: Basketball team, 1961, 1961 253A: Text copy from a year book of faculty members, c.1950
  - NEGATIVES, Box 231: See note for contents, RG0031 Series 1 (Box SHARED Box 15, Box 231)
    1: Pres. Carroll shaking hands with a man 2: Man speaking at a podium, c.1865 3: Ford's Theater and Old Medical School building on corner of 10th and E Streets, NW 4: Group of people talking to a man on a strecher 5: View of Virginia Ave, NW from Washington monument - vista west, c.1894 6: View of Virginia Ave, NW from Washington monument - vista west, c.1950 7: Hospital delivery room depicting procedure after the birth of an immature baby of Mr. and Mrs. William Stock - MISSING 5/01, 11/1952 8: Hospital delivery room scene, a new born baby carried by the staff - MISSING 5/01, 11/1952 9: Hospital delivery room scene, a new born baby carried by the staff, 11/1952 10: Hospital delivery room scene, a new born baby carried by the staff, 11/1952 11: Hospital delivery room scene, a new born baby carried by the staff, 11/1952 12: Hospital delivery room scene, a new born baby carried by the staff, 11/1952 13: Hospital delivery room scene, a new born baby carried by the staff, 11/1952 13: Hospital delivery room scene, a new born baby carried by the staff, 11/1952 14: Hospital delivery room scene, a new born baby carried by the staff, 11/1952 15: Hospital delivery room scene, a new born baby carried by the staff, 11/1952 16: Hospital delivery room scene, a new born baby carried by the staff, 11/1952 17: Hospital delivery room scene, a new born baby carried by the staff, 11/1952 18: People in nursery 19: Lisner library, Bell and Stuart Halls, c.1960 20: Inauguration of Pres. Carroll - setting up chairs in Yard, 5/3/1961 21: Inauguration of Pres. Carroll - Tin Tabernacle, 5/3/1961 22: Foreign students Christmas party, 1953, 12/1953 23: Foreign students Christmas party, 1953, 12/1953 24: Foreign students Christmas party, 1953, 12/1953 25: Mrs. O.S. Colclough, Prof. A. Deibert, Hana Macris, and Mr. Maionea at Foreign Students' Christmas Party, 12/10/54 26: Prof. A. Deibert, V. Kirkbride, Mrs. H.G. Doyle, H. Bakr, N. Shoaib, and T. Alit at Foreign Students Christmas Party 27: International Students Society Christmas Party, 1954, 12/1954 28: Inauguration of Pres.Carroll, 5/3/1961 29: Inauguration of Pres.Carroll, 5/3/1961 30: Inauguration of Pres.Carroll, 5/3/1961 31: Inauguration of Pres.Carroll, 5/3/1961 32: Inauguration of Pres.Carroll, 5/3/1961 33: Inauguration of Pres.Carroll, 5/3/1961 34: Inauguration of Pres.Carroll, 5/3/1961 35: Inauguration of Pres.Carroll, 5/3/1961 36: Inauguration of Pres.Carroll, 5/3/1961 37: Inauguration of Pres.Carroll, 5/3/1961 38: Inauguration of Pres.Carroll, 5/3/1961 39: Inauguration of Pres.Carroll, 5/3/1961 40: Inauguration of Pres.Carroll - President Kennedy walking in processional, 5/3/1961 41: Inauguration of Pres.Carroll, 5/3/1961 42: Inauguration of Pres.Carroll - stage, 5/3/1961 43: Inauguration of Pres.Carroll - stage, 5/3/1961 44: Inauguration of Pres.Carroll - crowd shots, 5/3/1961 45: Inauguration of Pres.Carroll - crowd shots, 5/3/1961 46: Inauguration of Pres.Carroll - stage, 5/3/1961 47: Inauguration of Pres.Carroll, 5/3/1961 48: Lisner Auditorium with houses on 21st and h Streets in background, 1953 49: Lisner Auditorium, 1953 50: Lisner Auditorium - three students standing in front, looking towards G Street 51: Lisner Auditorium, Troubadors in front of 52: Dean Elmer Louis Kayser's class of Civilization, lecturing in Lisner Auditorium, 1946 53: Law Day- Judge Jones, Dean Fay, Judge Stephens, Williams, Judge Danaker, William Archbold, 1955 54: Law Day- Judge Jones, Dean Fay, Judge Stephens, Williams, Judge Danaker, William Archbold, 1954 55: Law Day- Judge Jones, Dean Fay, Judge Stephens, Williams, Judge Danaker, William Archbold, 1954 56: Law Day- Assoc. Prof. Robert M. Cooper, seated Mr. Abram Chayes, Dr. Winfred Anerholser, Prof. of Psusciatry, Mr. Gerold O' Brien, 1954 57: Law Day- Edward Ansell, President of the Student Bar Association of the University, 1954 58: Law Day- Prof. Davidson, Simon Tucker, Richard S. Doyler, Kramer, Frank Reifsnyder, 1954 59: Law Day- Judge Walter Bastain. Oswald Calclaugh, Judge Marvin Jones, Mr. James Perlin, Judge Jones Kirkland, Godfrey Hunter, 1954 60: Student Activities- Law School, Institute on the Internal Revenue Code of 19654, University Law School, 1954 61: Student Activities- Law School, Institute on the Internal Revenue Code of 19654, University Law School, 1954 62: Student Activities- Law School, Institute on the Internal Revenue Code of 19654, University Law School, 1954 63: Student Activities- Law School, Institute on the Internal Revenue Code of 19654, University Law School, 1954 64: Student Activities- Law School, Institute on the Internal Revenue Code of 19654, University Law School, 1954 65: Student Activities- Law School, Institute on the Internal Revenue Code of 19654, University Law School, 1954 66: Students studying in Student Union, c.1965 67: David Brown as a Navy pilot (top row, second from right), c.1943 68: David Brown, U.S. Navy, Oct. 1943 69: Kapa Kapa Gama, 1964 70: Interfraternity Council, 1914 71: Greek House, 1915 72: Tin Tabernacle (gymnasium), c.1940 73: Corcoran Hall, c.1935 74: Stockton Hall, c.1930 75: Mabel Thurston, wearing a gown supposedly given to her by an aunt, c.1900 76: Thurston Hall, 1964 77: Mabel Thurston sitting in a chair, c.1930
  - NEGATIVES, Box 232: See note for contents, RG0031 Series 1 (Box SHARED Box 15, Box 232)
    1: Women's Board, Mrs. Robert H. Jackson, Mme. Hussien, Mrs. Harold H. Burton, Mrs. Cloyd H. Marvin, Mrs. Samuel B. Burgess, 1954 2: Women's Board, Mrs. Robert H. Jackson, Mme. Hussien, Mrs. Harold H. Burton, Mrs. Cloyd H. Marvin, Mrs. Samuel B. Burgess, 1954 3: Mrs. Conrad B. Myre, member of the Women's Board, modeling a gift shop apron. Appeared in 1957-58 issue of the Courier., Dec, 1947 4: Mrs. Cloyd H. Marvin, Mrs Gilbert S. Frankel, Mrs. Seymour Alpert, Thanks giving Tea, 1949 5: Medical School annual banquet Dr. Luther H. Snyder, Dr. Cloyd H. Mavin, and Dr. Henery Clay Corbett 6: Hospital Women's Board- Mrs. Gilbert Grosvenor, Mrs. Ellis Bell Miller, Mrs. John W. Brewer and Mrs W.E.Miller, 1949 7: Women's Board Thanks giving Tea, Mrs. Gilbert Grosvenor, Mrs. Ellis Bell, Miller, A. Mie, John W. Brewer, 11/51 8: Mrs. Seymour Alpert,and Mrs. F.F. Littlehelp Santa in the Hospital with new gift cart, 11/51 9: Mrs. Seymour Alpert,and Mrs. F.F. Littlehelp Santa in the Hospital with new gift cart, 11/51 10: Women's Board- Thanks giving Tea, Mrs. John W.Brewer signs up, Mrs. W.D. Terrell Jr., Mrs. Rugus M. Roll, 1949 11: Marion Moore, gives $75 for Social Services use to help out patients to Ms. Satah Haste and Mrs. Carolyn Parise, 2/52 12: Marion Moore, gives $75 for Social Services use to help out patients to Ms. Satah Haste and Mrs. Carolyn Parise, 2/52 13: Guanita Brocon, Mrs. Rt. Bolwell, Mrs. Gustav H. Emery, automatic glove conditioner, 6/51 14: Guanita Brocon, Mrs. Rt. Bolwell, Mrs. Gustav H. Emery, automatic glove conditioner, 6/51 15: Head nurse Mayori Anderson and Ward Helper Willie, Mrs Johnes demonstrates electric needle cleaner donated by the Women's Board, 6/51 16: Head nurse Mayori Anderson and Ward Helper Willie, Mrs Johnes demonstrates electric needle cleaner donated by the Women's Board, 6/51 17: Women's Board, The junior auxillary and the edvisers meet to make ffavors for tholiday hospital trays. Here they are making bacons, 5/51 18: Women's Board, The junior auxillary and the edvisers meet to make ffavors for tholiday hospital trays. Here they are making bacons, 5/51 19: Women's Board, The junior auxillary and the edvisers meet to make ffavors for tholiday hospital trays. Here they are making bacons, 5/51 20: Members of the Women's Board conduct tours through hospital. Here a group starts on tour on hospital day, 5/12/51 21: Members of the Women's Board conduct tours through hospital. Here a group starts on tour on hospital day, 5/12/51 22: President Cloyd H. Marvin, Mrs. Frank Russell, Mrs. Marvin & hospital, Victor Sudewig as women's Board of hospital presents a chec, 9/49 23: President Cloyd H. Marvin, Mrs. Frank Russell, Mrs. Marvin & hospital, Victor Sudewig as women's Board of hospital presents a chec, 9/49 24: Mrs. Walter A. Bloedorn and Mrs. Henry Alvah Strong, Thanks giving Tea, 1949 25: Mrs. Ruth Hocker, Mrs. Victor Ludewig, Mrs. David Williams, Miss Virginia Kirkbude, and Mrs Everett Johnson, Thanks giving Tea, 1949 26: Mrs. Walter A. Bloedorn, Mrs. Henry A. Strong, Mrs. Wilber Carr, Thanks giving Tea, 1949 27: Mrs. Wilber Carr and new silver service, Thanks giving Tea, 1949 28: Mrs. W.E. Miller and Mrs. Norman T. Anderson examine donations for giftshop, Thanks giving Tea, 1949 29: Mrs. Hertha McCully executive house keeper of the hospital, Mrs. Alexander Wetmore, Chairman of the Tea, and Mrs. Ruth Bernett, 1949 30: Mrs. Henry A. Strong and Mrs. Cloyd H. Marvin, Thanks giving Tea, 1949 31: President Marvin strolling through the Yard with baseball letterman BobReid of Arlington and Fritzi Nykopp, daughter of the minist, 1954 32: Pres. Marvin and John Hollup, basket ball star 33: Pres. Marvin, former president of the Student Council Bill Warner in stripped suit, and Charles Crechton, 1949 34: Charlie Metcalf and Barbara Healy were chosen King and Queen of the Mardi Grass Ball 35: Charlie Metcalf and Barbara Healy were chosen King and Queen of the Mardi Grass Ball 36: Medical School; D.R. Twins 37: Medical School; D.R. Twins 38: May Day Carnival, c.1948 39: Medical School-Bacteriology. Dr. Robbins-Courier, 06/1957 40: Medical School-Bacteriology. Dr. Robbins-Courier, 06/1957 41: Medical School-Bacteriology. Dr. Robbins-Courier, 06/1957 42: Medical School-Classrooms and Labs: W.G. McCarter, L.L. Michen, Dr. Angus MacIvor 43: Medical School-Classrooms and Labs: W.G. McCarter, L.L. Michen, Dr. Angus MacIvor 44: Medical School-Classrooms and Labs: W.G. McCarter, L.L. Michen, Dr. Angus MacIvor 45: Medical School-Biochemistry: Dr. Carleton Raymond Treadwell, adjusts the analytical balance, 03/1952 46: Medical School-Biochemistry: Dr. Carleton Raymond Treadwell, adjusts the analytical balance, 03/1952 47: Medical School-Biochemistry: Dr. Victor Shocken adjusts the working apparatus, 03/1952 48: Medical School-Biochemistry: Dr. Victor Shocken adjusts the working apparatus, 03/1952 49: Medical School-Pharmacology: Victor W. Rodwell, 02/1951 50: Pharmacology Department: Injecting a radio active drug into a mouse, 02/1951 51: Visit of Washington, Jr. Academy of Science to Medical School, 06/1956 52: Medical School, Audio Visual lab: Frank Delaney, 06/1960 53: Medical School, Audio Visual lab: Frank Delaney, 06/1960 54: Medical School, Audio Visual lab: Frank Delaney, 06/1960 55: Medical School, Audio Visual lab: Frank Delaney, 06/1960 56: Medical School, Audio Visual lab: Frank Delaney, 06/1960 57: Medical School, Audio Visual lab: Frank Delaney, 06/1960 58: Medical School, Audio Visual lab: Frank Delaney, 06/1960 59: Medical School, Audio Visual lab: Frank Delaney, 06/1960 60: Beaumont Society Banquet, 04/1956 61: Medical School Exteriors 62: Christmas at the Medical School 63: Christmas at the Medical School 64: Smith-Reed-Russell Society Banquet: Dean W.A. Bloedorn, Dr. Oscar Dodek, and Dr. Thomas A. Dooley 65: Smith-Reed-Russell Society Banquet: Dean W.A. Bloedorn, Dr. Oscar Dodek, and Dr. Thomas A. Dooley 66: Nell Weaver, Queen of May Day with Glenn L. Archer, President of the Student Council 67: Laboratory, Dr. Joseph Still watches as Dr. Melvin Heiffer examines the acidityof a blood sample collected in the research concer 68: Laboratory, Dr. Joseph Still watches as Dr. Melvin Heiffer examines the acidityof a blood sample collected in the research concer 69: Laboratory, Dr. Joseph Still watches as Dr. Melvin Heiffer examines the acidityof a blood sample collected in the research concer 70: Laboratory, Dr. Joseph Still watches as Dr. Melvin Heiffer examines the acidityof a blood sample collected in the research concer 71: Laboratory, Dr. Joseph Still watches as Dr. Melvin Heiffer examines the acidityof a blood sample collected in the research concer 72: Laboratory, Dr. Joseph Still watches as Dr. Melvin Heiffer examines the acidityof a blood sample collected in the research concer 73: Laboratory, Dr. Joseph Still watches as Dr. Melvin Heiffer examines the acidityof a blood sample collected in the research concer 74: Dr. George Gamow on the phone 75: Dr. George Gamow cartoon (his head coming out of a bottle) 76: Dr. George Gamow at the blackboard 77: Phi Beta Kappa - John Parks and E.K. Morris with two men 78: Unidentified man
  - NEGATIVES, Box 233: See note for contents, RG0031 Series 1 (Box SHARED Box 22, Box 233)